This inductee has received so many awards over his career, not just from the
Irish community,
or international business and universities and all, that he stopped accepting
them a
couple years ago. So it's really a treat to have Jack Kahl come here for him as
a personal
favor to accept this tonight. And in something, Jack is someone that all
Cleveland knows, Dan
Coughlin, he's come to Cleveland Sports for more than four decades. This is a
sport that's
rated for the playing dealer. He's been on channel eight since 1983. Twice
named Ohio
Sports Writer of the Year. He's an Emmy Award winner. He's traveled with the
Browns, the
Indians, covers some of the biggest college games of the 20th century,
including five
goals. He was ringside for the Albee-Fraser fight, which I'm very jealous about.
17 Indianapolis
500, his auto race, and all that. He's got three books out from his careers.
Let's have
another guest announce and create some papers to prove it. And I guarantee you,
if you pick
it up, the stories are about a page and a half long, and he'll read one and say,
"Okay,
I'm not going to do any more." And all of a sudden you read through the whole
book. And
it's like you're sitting at a bar with Dan, and he's telling you his great
stories. So
check it out. But we almost didn't have him here today, because he was driving
there in
Cleveland by the parking spot. So he's driving around, driving around, and he
started to pray.
He said, "Lord, if you find me a good parking spot, I'll give up drinking. I'll
go to the
future." Suddenly the clouds parted. The sun shone down at an empty spot right
by the
hotel. The meter was already paid. Dan said, "Lord, never mind. I found one."
[laughter]
[applause]